Diego Martin

Trinidad.

TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN

My name is Brian St. Bernard, twenty-eight (28) years of age and I would like to be

afforded an opportunity to work within your establishment to enhance my professional

skills while gaining experience in a dynamic work environment

My sound family background, together with my working experience have shaped and

equipped with the necessary skills and attributes which has allowed me to grow as an

individual, who is not only disciplined, but fully capable of adapting to a changing

environment so as to complete the task at hand.

I am respectful, honest, self-motivated and work oriented. I am dedicated to using the

skills that I have been taught in order to be an asset to your organization.

Enclosed to my resume for your perusal.

Thank you in advance as I await your response.

Respectively yours,

Brian St. Bernard

BRIAN ST. BERNARD

#70/2 Industrial Estate, Diego Martin Email: brianbernard6@gmail.com Tel: [868]633-3883 Cell:[868]308-1397/344-7715

CURRICULUM VITAE

PERSONAL:	
Date of Birth:	17 th March 1988
Marital Status:	Single

HOBBIES:

- > Interacting with people
- > Driving and site seeing
- > Tuning and Maintenance of Vehicles
- > Simply upgrading of vehicles

OBJECTIVE:

To secure a challenging position that allows for growth and development of my skills. I also have five (5) year experience in driving.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND:

Diego Martin Government Primary School	1993-2000
Belmont Junior Secondary	2000-2003
Mucurapo Secondary Comprehensive	2003-2005
CIP IT Training Services Provider	2007-2008

QUALIFICATION:

International Maritime Organization

Engine Room Rating

Engineering Rating Class 4

Seaman Class IV;

Areas: Personal Survival Techniques-basic

Fire Prevention 7 Fire Fighting- basic

Elementary First Aid

Personal Safety & Social Responsibilities

Nautical (Deck) knowledge

Introduction to Seamanship & Ropework

Ship Husbandry

	GRADE
Windows 98	Α
Microsoft Word 2000	Α
Excel 2000	Α
Access 2000	А

SKILLS:

- > Proficient in Microsoft Word
- > Familiar with Microsoft Excel and PowerPoint

WORK EXPERIENCE:

DDS Maintenance (roof maintenance personnel)	Sept 2005
Sun Way Construction (stock check)	Jan 2008
Collateral Security & Investigation Limited (Port officer)	Apr 2010
Royal Jordanian (Driver/Messenger)	2011-2014

- ➤ Driving agent to view Land/Houses
- > Collecting and delivering mail
- > Posting ad on newspaper

Crews Inn Hotel & Yachting Centre (Docksman) 2014-2015

- > Work in collaboration with Customs Officers
- > Take log of all boats that enters and leave from slips
- > Take log of any maintenance issue relating to the dock area
- > Inspection of Pedestal and dock area
- > Visual inspection of water level on vessel
- > Escorting foreigners to Customs and Immigration
- ➤ Mooring the boat to the dock

Albrosco 2015-2016

- > Receive orders from customers via Phone or from head office
- > Revised closing stock from previous day
- > Place order of goods to the stock department to meet daily sales demands
- > Load goods into Vehicle
- > Deliver goods to customers
- > Take note of customer queries or concern and report to Company
- > Write up a bill/receipt for customers
- > Receive cash from sales
- > Take record of credit sales
- > Balance stock and sales sheets
- Liaise with Account Department and sales manager to facilitate effective customers' service

> Transport goods in western and Eastern district

STRENGTHS:

> Generally Knowledge and can defect advance vehicular problem

Tel: 315-0444

- > Excellent written and oral communication skills
- > Meticulous attention to details
- > Works well with others
- Success motivated

REFERENCES:

Ms. Monique Thomas
Ministry of Finance
Business Operation Assistance II(BOA II)